American Civil Liberties Union Records: Subgroup 2, Organizational Matters Series, 1947-1995: Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Special Collections.
- Series 1: Organizational Matters, 1930-1995; 582 boxes
  - Subseries 1C: Board Committees, 1941-1990; 102 boxes
    - Censorship Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1949; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Civil Rights in American Colonies Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1949; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Civil Rights in American Colonies Committee, Guam, 1949; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Civil Rights in American Colonies Committee, Puerto Rico, 1949; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Civil Rights in American Colonies Committee, Virgin Islands, 1948-1949; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - Civil Rights in Labor Relations, Minutes and Reports, 1948-1949; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 13)
    - Civil Rights in Labor Relations, Correspondence and related materials, 1948-1949; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 14)
    - Indian Civil Rights Committee, Minutes, 1949; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 15)
    - Indian Civil Rights Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1949; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 16)
    - International Civil Liberties Committee, Minutes, 1949; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 17)
    - International Civil Liberties Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1949; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 18)
    - National Council on Freedom from Censorship, Minutes and Statements, 1949; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 19)
    - National Council on Freedom from Censorship, Correspondence and related materials, 1949; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 20)
    - Race Relations Committee, Minutes, 1949; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 21)
    - Race Relations Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1949; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 22)
    - Radio Committee, Minutes, 1949; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 23)
    - Radio Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1949; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 24)
    - Women's Committee, 1949; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 25)
    - Standing Committees, Roster, 1950; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 26)
    - Emergency Policy Committee Meeting, Minutes, 1950; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 27)
    - Academic Freedom Committee, Minutes and By-Laws, 1950; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 28)
    - Academic Freedom Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1950; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 29)
    - Alien Civil Rights Committee, Minutes, 1950; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 30)
    - Alien Civil Rights Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1950; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 31)
    - Civil Rights in American Colonies, Correspondence and related materials, 1950; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 32)
    - Civil Rights in American Colonies, Guam, 1950; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 33)
    - Civil Rights in American Colonies, Virgin Islands, 1950; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 34)
    - Indian Civil Rights Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1950; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 35)
    - International Civil Liberties, Minutes, 1950; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 36)
    - International Civil Liberties, Correspondence and related materials, 1950; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 37)
    - National Council on Freedom of Expression, Minutes and By-Laws, 1950; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 38)
    - National Council on Freedom of Expression, Correspondence and related materials, 1949-1950; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 39)
    - Academic Freedom Committee, Minutes, 1951; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Civil Rights in Labor Relations Committee, Minutes, 1951; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Committee Evaluations, 1951; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 2a)
    - Freedom of Expression/Conscience, Committee on, Minutes, 1951; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - International Civil Liberties Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1951; 2 folders (Box 78, Folder 4-5)
    - National Council on Freedom from Censorship, Minutes, 1951; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Radio Committee, Minutes, 1951; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Sub-Committee of Radio Committee, Minutes, 1951; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Women's Rights Committee, 1951; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Academic Freedom Committee, Minutes, 1952; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - Academic Freedom Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1952; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Alien Civil Rights Committee, Minutes, 1952; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - Censorship Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1952; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - Civil Rights in Labor Relations Committee, Minutes, 1952; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 14)
    - Due Process Committee, Minutes, 1952; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 15)
    - Due Process Committee, Memoranda, 1952; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 16)
    - Freedom of Expression/Religion/Conscience, Minutes, 1952; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 17)
    - International Civil Liberties Committee, Minutes, 1952; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 18)
    - International Civil Liberties Committee on, Correspondence and related materials, 1952; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 19)
    - Membership and Affiliates Committee, Minutes, 1952; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 20)
    - National Council on Freedom from Censorship, Minutes, 1952; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 21)
    - Nominations Committee, Memoranda, 1952; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 22)
    - Public Relations Committee, Minutes, 1952; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 23)
    - Public Relations Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1952; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 24)
    - Radio Committee, Minutes, 1952; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 25)
    - Academic Freedom Committee, Minutes and Roster, 1953; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 26)
    - Academic Freedom Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1953; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 27)
    - Alien Civil Rights Committee, Minutes, 1953; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 28)
    - Alien Civil Rights Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1953; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 29)
    - Censorship Council, Correspondence and related materials, 1953; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 30)
    - Advisory Council, Correspondence and related materials, 1953; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 31)
    - Colonies Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1953; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 32)
    - Due Process Committee, Minutes, 1953; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 33)
    - Freedom of Expression/Religion/Conscience, Minutes, 1953; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 34)
    - International Civil Liberties, Committee on, Minutes, 1953; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 35)
    - International Civil Liberties, Committee on, Correspondence and related materials, 1953; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 36)
    - Labor Committee, Minutes, 1953; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 37)
    - Membership and Affiliates Committee, Minutes, 1953; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 38)
    - National Council on Freedom from Censorship, Minutes, 1953; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 39)
    - National Council on Freedom from Censorship, Right of Access to News Sources - Subcommittee, 1953; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 40)
    - National Security Committee, Minutes, 1953; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 41)
    - Public Relations Committee, Minutes, 1953; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 42)
    - Public Relations Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1953; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 43)
    - Race Relations Committee, 1953; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 44)
    - Radio Committee, Minutes, 1953; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 45)
    - Special Lamont Committee, Lamont, Corliss, 1953; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 45a)
    - Women's Rights Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1953; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 46)
    - Academic Freedom Committee, Minutes, 1954; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 47)
    - Academic Freedom Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1954; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 48)
    - American Colonies Committee, Application of Federal Law to Puerto Rico, 1954; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 49)
    - American Colonies Committee, 1954; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 50)
    - American Colonies Committee, Virgin Islands, 1954; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 51)
    - Due Process Committee, Minutes, 1954; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 52)
    - Free Speech and Association Committee, Censorship Panel, 1954; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 53)
    - Freedom of Expression/Religion/Conscience, Minutes, 1954; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 54)
    - International Civil Liberties, Minutes, 1954; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Labor, Minutes, 1954; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Labor, Correspondence and related materials, 1954; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - National Council on Freedom from Censorship, Minutes, 1954; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - National Security Committee, Minutes, 1954; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Public Relations Committee, Minutes, 1954; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Public Relations Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1954; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Radio Committee, Minutes, 1954; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Membership, Finance and Administration, Correspondence and related materials, 1954; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Committee Structural Changes, 1954-1955; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - Academic Freedom Committee, Minutes, 1955; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - Academic Freedom Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1955; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - Alien Civil Rights Panel, Minutes, 1955; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 13)
    - Alien Civil Rights Panel, Correspondence and related materials, 1955; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 14)
    - American Colonies Committee, 1955; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 15)
    - Censorship Panel, Minutes, 1955; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 16)
    - Censorship Panel, Subcommittee on Motion Picture Censorship, Correspondence, 1955; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 17)
    - Church-State Panel, Correspondence and related materials, 1955; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 18)
    - Due Process Committee, Minutes, 1955; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 19)
    - Due Process Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1955; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 20)
    - Indian Civil Rights Panel of Due Process Committee, Minutes, 1955; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 21)
    - Due Process Committee, Indian Civil Rights Panel, 1955; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 22)
    - Due Process Committee, Race-Creed and National Origin Panel, Minutes, 1955; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 23)
    - Due Process Committee, Race-Creed and National Origin Panel, Correspondence, 1955; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 24)
    - Due Process Committee, Women's Panel, 1955; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 25)
    - Freedom of Speech and Association Committee, Minutes, 1955; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 26)
    - Freedom of Speech and Association Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1955; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 27)
    - Freedom of Speech and Association Committee, Censorship Panel, 1955; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 28)
    - Freedom of Speech and Association Committee, Radio-TV Panel, Minutes, 1955; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 29)
    - Freedom of Speech and Association Committee, Radio-TV Panel, Correspondence and Related Material, 1955; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 30)
    - International Civil Liberties Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1955; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 31)
    - Labor Committee, Minutes, 1955; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 32)
    - Labor Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1955; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 33)
    - Radio-Television Panel, Minutes, 1955; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 34)
    - Membership, Finance and Administration Committee, Minutes, 1955; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 35)
    - Membership, Finance and Administration Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1955; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 36)
    - Board Committees, General, 1956; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 37)
    - Academic Freedom Committee, Minutes, 1956; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 38)
    - Academic Freedom Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1956; 2 folders (Box 79, Folder 39-40)
    - American Colonies Committee, Okinawa Panel, 1956; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 41)
    - Censorship Panel, Minutes, 1956; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Censorship Panel, Correspondence and related materials, 1956; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Censorship Panel, Subcommittee on Motion Picture Censorship, Minutes, 1956; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Censorship Panel, Subcommittee on Motion Picture, Censorship Correspondence, 1956; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Censorship Panel, Library Book Selections, Correspondence and related materials, 1953-1956; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Due Process Committee, Minutes, 1956; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Due Process Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1956; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Free Speech Association, Minutes, 1956; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Free Speech Association, Correspondence and related materials, 1956; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - International Civil Liberties Committee, 1956; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Labor Committee, Minutes, 1956; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - Labor Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1956; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - Nomination Committee, 1956; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 13)
    - Race Relations Panel, 1956; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - Radio-TV Committee, Minutes, 1956; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 15)
    - Radio-TV Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1956; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 16)
    - Religion Panel, Minutes, 1956; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 17)
    - Religion Panel, Correspondence and related materials, 1956; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 18)
    - Academic Freedom Committee, Minutes, 1957; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 19)
    - Academic Freedom Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1957; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 20)
    - Censorship Committee, Minutes, 1957; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 21)
    - Civil Liberties in United States Territories, Minutes, 1957; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 22)
    - Civil Liberties in United States Territories, Correspondence and related materials, 1957; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 23)
    - Due Process Committee, Minutes, 1957; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 24)
    - Free Speech Committee, Minutes, 1957; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 25)
    - Indian Civil Rights Committee, Minutes, 1957; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 26)
    - Labor Committee, Minutes, 1957; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 27)
    - Public Relations Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1957; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 28)
    - Radio-TV Committee, Minutes, 1957; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 29)
    - Wright Security Commission, Correspondence and related materials, 1957; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 30)
    - Academic Freedom Committee, Minutes, 1958; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 31)
    - Academic Freedom Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1958; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 32)
    - Censorship Panel, Subcommittee on Local Obscenity Prosecutions, 1958; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 33)
    - Committee on U.S. Territories, Minutes, 1958; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 34)
    - Due Process Committee, Minutes, 1958; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 35)
    - Due Process Committee, FBI Study, 1955-1958; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 36)
    - Equality Committee, Minutes, 1958; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 37)
    - Indian Civil Rights Committee, Minutes, 1958; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 38)
    - Free Speech Committee, Minutes, 1958; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 39)
    - Indian Civil Rights Commission, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1958; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 40)
    - Labor Committee, Minutes, 1958; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 41)
    - Labor Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1958; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 42)
    - Okinawa Panel, Correspondence and related materials, 1958; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 43)
    - Public Relations Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1958; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 44)
    - Radio-TV Committee, Minutes, 1958; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 45)
    - Wright Security Commission Report, Correspondence and related materials, 1958; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 46)
    - Academic Freedom Committee, Minutes, 1959; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Academic Freedom Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1959; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Academic Freedom Committee, Academic Freedom in New Colleges and Universities, 1959; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Academic Freedom Committee, Advisory Council, 1959; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Academic Freedom Committee, Nominating Sub-Committee, 1959; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Censorship Committee, Minutes, 1959; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Censorship Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1959; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Church and State Committee, Minutes, 1959; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Church and State Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1959; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - Civil Liberties in U.S. Territories, Correspondence and related materials, 1959; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - Due Process Committee, Minutes, 1959; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - Due Process Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1959; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 12)
    - Equality Committee, Minutes, 1959; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 13)
    - Equality Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1959; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 14)
    - Freedom of Speech and Association Committee, Minutes, 1959; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 15)
    - Freedom of Speech and Association Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1959; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 16)
    - Indian Civil Rights Committee, Minutes, 1959; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 17)
    - Indian Civil Rights Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1959; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 18)
    - International Civil Liberties Committee, 1959; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 19)
    - Labor Committee, Minutes, 1959; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 20)
    - Labor Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1959; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 21)
    - Public Relations Committee, Minutes and related materials, 1959; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 22)
    - Public Relations Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1959; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 23)
    - Radio-TV Committee, Minutes, 1959; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 24)
    - Radio-TV Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1959; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 25)
    - Tax Deductibility Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1959; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 26)
    - Affiliates/Finance/Administration Committee, 1959; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 27)
    - Nominating Committee, 1959; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 28)
    - Academic Freedom Committee, Minutes, 1960; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 29)
    - Academic Freedom Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1960; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 30)
    - Censorship Committee, Minutes, 1960; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 31)
    - Church and State Committee, Minutes, 1960; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 32)
    - Church and State Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1960; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 33)
    - Church and State, Subcommittee on Religious Education in Public Schools, 1960; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 34)
    - Due Process Committee, Minutes, 1960; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 35)
    - Due Process Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1960; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 36)
    - Equality Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1960; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 37)
    - Free Speech and Association Committee, Minutes, 1960; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Free Speech and Association Committee, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1960; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Indian Civil Rights Committee, Minutes, 1960; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Indian Civil Rights Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1960; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Labor Committee, Minutes, 1960; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Labor Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1960; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Radio/TV Committee, Minutes, 1960; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Tax Deductibility Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1960; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - Academic Freedom Committee, Minutes, 1961; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - Academic Freedom Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1961; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - Academic Freedom Committee, Fulbright Subcommittee, Correspondence and related materials, 1961; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 11)
    - Administration Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1961; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 12)
    - Censorship Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1961; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 13)
    - Church and State Committee, Minutes, 1961; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 14)
    - Church and State Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1961; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 15)
    - Church and State Committee, Working Papers, 1961; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 16)
    - Church and State Committee, Subcommittee Funds for Religiously-Controlled Schools, 1961; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 17)
    - Church and State Committee, Subcommittee on Religious Education in Public Schools, 1961; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 18)
    - Committee to Nominate New Executive Director, Minutes and Memoranda, 1961; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 18a)
    - Committee to Nominate New Executive Director, Correspondence, 1961; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 18b)
    - Due Process Committee, Minutes, 1961; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 19)
    - Equality Committee, Minutes, 1961; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 20)
    - Equality Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1961; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 21)
    - Free Speech and Association Committee, Minutes, 1961; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 22)
    - Free Speech and Association Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1961; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 23)
    - Indian Civil Rights Committee, Minutes, 1961; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 24)
    - Indian Civil Rights Committee, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1961; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 25)
    - International Civil Liberties Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1961; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 26)
    - Labor Committee, Minutes, 1961; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 27)
    - Labor Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1961; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 28)
    - Nominating Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1961; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 29)
    - Radio-TV Committee, Minutes, 1961; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 30)
    - Radio-TV Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1961; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 31)
    - Board Committees, General Correspondence and related materials, 1962; 2 folders (Box 83, Folder 1-2)
    - Academic Freedom Committee, Minutes and Roster, 1962; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Academic Freedom Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1962; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Administration Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1962; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Censorship Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1962; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Church and State Committee, Minutes and Roster, 1962; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Church and State Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1962; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - Due Process Committee, Minutes, 1962; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Due Process Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1962; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - Equality Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1962; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - Executive Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1962; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 12)
    - Free Speech Committee, Minutes, 1962; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 13)
    - Free Speech Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1962; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 14)